Guide to the Dept. of Marketing and Communications records, 1997-2011.
Johnson Graduate School of Management Dept. of Marketing and Communications records, 1997-2011
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Johnson Graduate School of Management Dept. of Marketing and Communications records, 1997-2011.
26-9-3260
Johnson Graduate School of Management (Cornell University). Dept. of Marketing and Communications.
6.4 cubic ft.
Publicity material, photographs, reports, periodicals, plans, proposals, directories, and handbooks.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes publicity material, photographs, annual and placement reports, marketing periodicals, plans and proposals, directories and handbooks relating to the Johnson Graduate School of Management.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes publicity material, photographs, annual and placement reports, marketing periodicals, plans and proposals, directories and handbooks relating to the Johnson Graduate School of Management.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Johnson Graduate School of Management (Cornell University). Dept. of Marketing and Communications.; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University--Faculty.; Johnson Graduate School of Management (Cornell University)--Publicity.; Johnson Graduate School of Management (Cornell University)
Subjects:
Business schools--New York (State)--Ithaca; Management--Study and teaching--New York (State)--Ithaca.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
Videotapes.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Publicity
  - Johnson Graduate School of Management, Early 1990's - 2003 (Box 1)
    Newsletters, flyers, brochures, posters, pamphlets, announcements
  - Johnson Graduate School of Management, Early 1990's - 2003 (Box 2)
  - Publicity booklet- Johnson Graduate School, ca. 1998 (Box 5)
  - Cornell Business newsletter, August 17, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Johnson Graduate School of Management, Early 1990's - 2004 (Box 6)
  - Johnson Graduate School - Newsletters, flyers, brochures, posters, pamphlets, including annual reports (2005-2011), 2004-2011 (Box 7)
- Series II. Photographs
  - Guest Speakers; A-D (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Guest Speakers; E-H (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Guest Speakers; I-K (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Guest Speakers; L (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Guest Speakers; M (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Guest Speakers; N-P (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Guest Speakers; R (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Guest Speakers; S (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Guest Speakers; S (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Guest Speakers; S (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Guest Speakers; T-W (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Guest Speakers; W (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Class Speakers, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Class Speakers-Stan Smith's Class (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
  - EDP, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - EDP, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - EDP, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - EDP, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - EDP, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - EDP, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - EDP, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - EDP Summer, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - EDP Summer, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Executive Authors (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Executive; Harold Green; David Hourer (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Executive Interviews; Irving Kristol; Thomas Murphy; Roy Park; David Rockefeller; James Schlesinger; Lewis Thomas; Gustavo Vollmer; Walter Wriston (Box 3, Folder 27-30)
  - Executive Photos-Foreign Products (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Alumni Group Shots (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Alumni Executive Council; AEC Mtg. 1989; AEC Mtg. April 88 NYC; AEC Mtg. May 1987; AEC Mtg. July 1986; AEC Photos May 85; AEC Mtg. Nov. 1984, 1984-1989 (Box 3, Folder 33-37)
  - Alumni/Johnson School Rochester Club (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Annual Fund; CGSM Fund (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Class and Club Officers Meetings; Class and Officers Mtg. Feb. 21-22, 1991; Class and Club Officers Mtg. May 1987; AEC Mtg. Sept. 15, 1989; Class and Club Officers Mtg. Sept. 8, 1988, 1987-1981 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - JGSM Clubs; 1986: JGSM Club of New York City; Washington Club, 1987-1981 (Box 3, Folder 41-42)
  - Best Business Schools (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Career Services Job Fair; Job Fair, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Classroom Shots; Ben Daniels' Entrepreneur Class Lectures; Oral & Written Communications; Classroom shots-various; Ethics Dilemmas in Management Course 1984; Classroom 1984; Classroom shots 1987-88, 1984-1988 (Box 3, Folder 45-50)
  - Commencement, 1984-1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1984-1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Follies, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Japanese Student Interns (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Pre-Tower Club Dinner, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Recruiting, 1984, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Sports scenes; basketball, various, intramural, hockey game-faculty and students, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 7-9)
  - Professors and Students (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Sound Investments, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Student Groups, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Student Groups, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Student Groups, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Student Groups, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Student Groups, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Student Groups, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Student Groups, Spring, Fall, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Student Groups, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Student Groups, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Student Groups, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Student Groups, 1970s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Student Groups, 1970s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 23-28)
  - Student Groups, 1960s (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Student Presentations (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Summer Internships, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Malott Resources - Computers, VAX Facility, Meyer Computing Lab (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Johnson School Library; JGSM Library; B & PA Library-Old Photos; Malott Library-New Optical Disk; GSM Libe-recent photos (Box 4, Folder 33-34)
  - Art Gallery (Box 4, Folder 35-40)
  - Hall of Honor; B & PA Hall of Honor; Miscellaneous; Hall of Honor-Schaenen (Box 4, Folder 41-46)
  - Mallot Hall; Mallot-inside; Mallot new wing dedication (Box 4, Folder 47-51)
  - At Play (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Public Program Photos (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Willard Straight Hall Reading Room (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Reunion, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 55-58)
  - Reunion, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Reunion, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
  - Reunion, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Reunion, Gerald R. Ford, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 5-7)
  - Reunion, Henry Kissinger, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 8-10)
  - Reunion, William F. Buckley, Sloan Dinner, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 11-15)
  - Reunion, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 16-19)
  - Brussels 86; Paris 87, London 88, Brussels 89, The Johnson School's First Asian Program Tokyo 89, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 20-25)
  - Reunion, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 26-29)
  - Reunion, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 30-31)
  - Students; Soviet Visitors, Frozen Assets, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Students; April Hosting Program, JGSM Placement and Recruiters Guide, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Students; April Hosting Program, JGSM Placement and Recruiters Guide, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Student Portraits (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Series III. Ephemera
  - Class of 1948 Reunion T-Shirt (Box 5)
  - "Pipeline to the 21st Century: Changing the Face of Corporate America"-PhotoSynthesis Producations, October 16, 2003; V-6267 (Box 7)
  - "CEO Exchange"-PBS Video, 2000; V-6268 (Box 7)